(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
桃鈴ねね 3D LIVE "Liminal"
[Visual: Momosuzu Nene 3D LIVE "Liminal"]
“いっせーのー”
"One, two, three"
で鳴り響いたスタートの合図
the starting signal rang out
なぞった線で結んだ世界
In a world connected by traced lines
色付けていく ここから
I'll add color, from here on
物心がつく頃 すでに此処にあった
By the time I was old enough to know better, it was already here
僕じゃない誰かの記憶は
Someone else's memory that isn't mine
夕陽とともに蘇る
Comes back with the sunset
古ぼけた絵本を取り出して
I took out an old picture book
落書きの中に1つの答えを見つけた
And found one answer in the scribbles
自分の価値に 目を疑って
I doubt the value of myself
どこまでだって 堕ちていけるの
How far can I fall?
どこか遠くに 消えてしまいたい
I want to disappear somewhere far away
こんな世界じゃ 僕はいらない
In a world like this, I'm not needed
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
"One, two, three" raising my voice
聴こえてくるんだ 自分の影の長さに気付く
I can hear it, I notice the length of my own shadow
もうこんな時間だ
It's already this time
一等星が顔を出した 届きそうで手を伸ばした
The first magnitude star has appeared, I reached out as if I could reach it
次は僕に着いてきなよ どんな暗闇でも
Next, follow me, no matter what darkness
(もういいかい？まーだだよ)
(Are you ready yet? Not yet)
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has begun to rise
(もういいかい？まーだだよ)
(Are you ready yet? Not yet)
色付けていく ここから
I'll add color, from here on
10年後の僕らはすれ違いばかりで
Ten years from now, we'll just pass each other by
幻想に想いを馳せては
And while longing for fantasies
“戻れない”そう思いこんだ
I became convinced that "I can't go back"
くたびれた心に追い討ちを
Adding insult to my tired heart
あの頃と変わらない夕陽も
The sunset that hasn't changed since those days
なんとも思わない
I don't think anything of it
自分を信じ 歩いていければ
If I could just believe in myself and keep walking
どこまでだって 昇れるのにな
I could climb as high as I want, you know
カットを跨ぐ その空白に 大切なモノ 見落としている
In that gap that crosses the cut, you're missing something important
見つけられないと泣きわめく君へ
To you who cries and screams that you can't find it
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
"One, two, three" raising my voice
聴こえてくるんだ 自分の影の長さに気付く
I can hear it, I notice the length of my own shadow
もうこんな時間だ
It's already this time
一等賞で駆け抜ける君
You running through in first place
くっついていただけの僕でも
Even though I was just clinging on
君の前を歩けるかな？
Can I walk in front of you?
こんな頼りない僕でも
Even though I'm this unreliable
宝箱はホコリをかぶったまま
The treasure chest remained covered in dust
無くした鍵はずっと 君のポケットの中にあった
The lost key was always in your pocket
散らばっていた全てが 今ひとつに重なる
Everything that was scattered now overlaps into one
手を取り 始めよう 僕たちの物語
Let's take hands and start our story
一度はいらないと思った 今なら胸を張れる気がしたんだ
I once thought I didn't need it, but now I feel like I can hold my head high
愛おしくて 掛け声はいつも
It's so dear to me, the shout is always
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
"One, two, three" raising my voice
聴こえてくるんだ 自分の影の長さに気付く
I can hear it, I notice the length of my own shadow
もうこんな時間だ
It's already this time
一等星が顔を出した 届きそうで手を伸ばした
The first magnitude star has appeared, I reached out as if I could reach it
次は僕に着いてきなよ どんな暗闇でも
Next, follow me, no matter what darkness
(もういいかい？まーだだよ)
(Are you ready yet? Not yet)
泣きじゃくった声で
With a voice choked with tears
笑う君が見えた
I could see you laughing
“いっせーのー”
"One, two, three"
で鳴り響いたスタートの合図
the starting signal rang out
なぞった線で結んだ世界
In a world connected by traced lines
色付けていく ここから
I'll add color, from here on
かくれんぼ / 作詞: TKT 作曲: EREN
[Title: Kakurenbo / Lyrics: TKT, Composition: EREN]
物心がつく頃
By the time I was old enough to know better
すでに此処にあった
It was already here
歌わない誰かの記憶は
The memories of someone who doesn't sing...
夕陽と共に甦る
...revive along with the setting sun.
古ぼけた絵本を取り出して
Taking out an old, worn-out picture book,
落書きの中に一つの
I found a single answer
答えを見つけた
within the scribbles.
自分の価値を疑って
Doubting my own worth,
どこまでだって落ちていけるの
how far can I fall?
どこか遠くに消えてしまいたい
I want to disappear somewhere far away,
こんな世界じゃ僕は要らない
in a world like this I'm not needed.
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun.
いっせーのーで声を挙げて
All together now, raise your voice,
聞こえてくるんだ
and it will be heard.
自分の影の長さに気付く
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already that time.
理想が顔を出した
Ideals showed their face,
届きそうで手を伸ばした
I reached out as if I could touch them.
次は僕に付いてきなよ
Next, come with me,
どんな暗闇でも
no matter how dark it gets.
もう一回、まだだよ
One more time, not yet,
幕は上がりだした
the curtain has begun to rise.
もう一回、まだだよ
One more time, not yet,
色付いてくここから
things will take color from here.
十年後の僕らは
Ten years later, we...
すれ違いばかりで
...keep passing each other by.
幻想に思いを馳せては
Lost in our illusions,
戻れないそう思い込んだ
we're convinced we can't go back.
くたびれた心に追い打ちを
Dealing a further blow to a weary heart.
あの頃と変わらない勇気も
Even that unchanging courage...
何とも思わない
...doesn't mean anything anymore.
自分を信じ歩いていければ
If I could believe in myself and keep walking,
どこまでだって登れるのに
I could climb anywhere, and yet...
葛藤を跨ぐその空白に
In that void stepping over conflict,
大切なもの見落としている
I'm overlooking what's important.
見つけられないと泣き喚く君へ
To you, crying out that you can't find it.
いっせーのーで声を挙げて
All together now, raise your voice,
聞こえてくるんだ
and it will be heard.
自分の影の長さに気付く
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already that time.
一緒で駆け抜ける君に
Even if I was just clinging to you
くっ付いてただけの僕でも
as you ran through,
君の前を歩けるかな
I wonder if I can walk in front of you,
こんな頼りない僕でも
even as unreliable as I am.
宝箱は埃を被ったまま失くした
The treasure chest was lost, still covered in dust.
鍵はずっと君のポケットの中にあった
The key was in your pocket all along.
散らばってた全てが今一つに重なる
All the scattered pieces now become one.
手を取り始めよう僕たちの物語
Let's take hands and begin our story.
宝箱はいらないと笑ったまま失くした
Saying I didn't need it, I lost it with a smile.
鍵は僕の胸でも今も鳴り出した
The key has begun to ring in my chest.
散らばってた全てが愛おしくて
Everything that was scattered is so precious,
今一つに重なる 歓声はいつも
now it all overlaps. The cheers are always...
いっせーのーで声を挙げて
All together now, raise your voice,
all together now, raise your voice,
聞こえてくるんだ
and it will be heard.
自分の影の長さに気付く
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already that time.
理想が顔を出した
Ideals showed their face,
届きそうで手を伸ばした
I reached out as if I could touch them.
次は僕に付いてきなよ
Next, come with me,
どんな暗闇でも
no matter how dark it gets.
もう一回、まだだよ
One more time, not yet,
泣きそうな歌声で
with a voice about to cry.
もう一回、まだだよ
One more time, not yet,
笑う君が見えた
I saw you laughing.
もう一回、まだだよ
One more time, not yet,
幕は上がりだした
the curtain has begun to rise.
もう一回、もういいよ
One more time, it's okay now,
色付いてくここから
things will take color from here.
曇天
[Title: Donten]
鉛の空 重く垂れ込み
The leaden sky hangs low and heavy...
鉛の空
Leaden sky
重く垂れ込め
Hanging low and heavy
真っ白に淀んだ
Stagnant in pure white
太陽が砕けて
The sun shatters
耳鳴りを
Making my ears
尖らせる
Ring sharply
ゆるりゆるり
Slowly, slowly
低いツバメが
The low-flying swallows
8の字なぞって
Tracing the figure eight
ビルの谷を駆ける
Race through the valleys of buildings
もうじきに
Very soon
夕立が来る
The evening shower will come
曇天の道を
On this path under cloudy skies
傘を忘れて
Having forgotten my umbrella
歩く彼女は
That girl walking there
雨に怯えてる
Is frightened by the rain
ので僕も
And so I too
弱虫ぶら下げて
Hanging my cowardice
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky
あちらこちら
Here and there
あんよはじょうず
Taking skillful steps
珈琲屋に寄って
Dropping by a coffee shop
一休み決めたら
Once I decide to take a break
帰れない
I can't go home
帰らない
I won't go home
曇天の道を
On this path under cloudy skies
ぶらりぶらぶら
Wandering aimlessly
歩く二人は
The two of us walking
足軽のごとく
Are like foot soldiers
危険好きの
Pretending to be
誰かのふりをする
Someone who loves danger
臆病者共
Cowards that we are
曇天の道を
On this path under cloudy skies
傘を忘れて
Having forgotten my umbrella
歩く彼女は
That girl walking there
雨に怯えてる
Is frightened by the rain
ので僕も
And so I too
弱虫ぶら下げて
Hanging my cowardice
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky
放っといて育つものなんだ
It's something that grows if you leave it alone
なんだろう？
I wonder what it is?
one more chance, one more chance
never never give up!
never give up!
運営さん、なんか放送、エコーが切れてるかもしれないとのことで確認をお願いします！
Staff, it seems the echo in the broadcast might be
off, so please check it!
出会いましては簡単すぎるよ
Meeting you was way too easy
最初に決めた答えはひとつ
The answer I decided on is just one
ときめきました合格しますか？
Will my heart race and pass the test?
恋も勝負もあわてない
In love and competition, I'm not rushing
コツコツコツと徹夜に溜息
Tick, tick, tick, I'm sighing through the night
私のなかに天才dreamer
Inside me, a genius dreamer
思うことみな叶えばいいな
I wish all my thoughts could come true
他人の世界はきにしない
I don't care about the world around me
Perfect-area complete!
絶対ここで待ってるんだ
I'm definitely waiting right here
Perfect-area 望む声が聞こえるよ
I can hear the voices wishing for the perfect area
ah! EAR EAR!!
Why? とまらないすれちがい
Why? This misunderstanding won't stop
私が相談相手なら
If I'm your sounding board
「友達かい？」「友達です。」
"Just friends?" "We're friends."
悲しき0点だね
It's a sad zero score, huh?
No! やりなおしかきなおし
No! Let's redo it, let's start over
本気で one more chance please
Seriously, one more chance please
いまより素敵な未来があるのに
There's a wonderful future ahead of me
いまより素敵に my life, my life, my life!!
My life can be even better, my life, my life, my life!!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
願いましたよ月にも星にも
I wished upon the moon and the stars
科学的にはどうにもならず
But scientifically, it doesn't matter
かがやき増したあしたを夢みて
I'm dreaming of a shining tomorrow
恋でガマンを学んだね
In love, I learned to endure
ムクムクムクと広がる雨雲
Fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, the rain clouds spread wide
私をぬらす瞬間squall
In a moment, a squall drenches me
悩みごとほら流れたみたい
Look, my worries seem to flow away
泣き言なんて忘れよう
I'll forget my complaints
Passive-nature conversation!
感動したいもっとずっと
I want to be moved, forever more
Passive-nature 自分次第変かわれるよ
Passive-nature, I can change myself
hi! EAR EAR!!
Perfect-area complete!
[Song: Perfect-area complete!]
ハイヤイヤ
Hai-ya-ya
さりげなく 聞いてみた
Casually, I tried asking.
私の勉強不足で
With my lack of studying,
可能性 ありますか?
is there a possibility?
試験は何点かな?
What score will the exam be?
Yay! 誰だって 意味だって
Yay! Whoever it is, whatever the meaning,
間に合うギリギリでしょ
is just barely in time, right?
これから 始まる 季節に挨拶
A greeting to the season that is about to begin.
これから 始める My Life, My Life, My Life!
I'm starting now, My Life, My Life, My Life!
気がついた 時には
By the time I realized it,
生まれてた なぜだろう?
it was already born, I wonder why?
さあね 意識は
Well, you see, consciousness
もう育ちつつあるよ
is already growing,
強く強くね
Stronger and stronger.
Wait 止まらない この気持ち
Wait, this feeling won't stop,
私の勉強不足で
With my lack of studying,
可能性 ありますか?
is there a possibility?
それとも 0点かな?
Or will it be zero?
No! やり直し 書き直し
No! Redo it, rewrite it,
本気で まんまジャンピング
Seriously, just as I am, jumping.
今より 素敵な 未来があるから
Because there's a future more wonderful than now,
今より 素敵に My Life, My Life, My Life!
More wonderfully than now, My Life, My Life, My Life!
はい！というわけで始まりました！
Alright! And so it has begun!
2026年桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ、イェーイ！
2026 Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live, Yay!
みんな、コメントも見えてるよ！ありがとう！
Everyone, I can see your comments! Thank you!
エコー気づいてくれた人ありがとう！
Thank you to those who noticed the echo!
ねね、今回3Dライブだから！
Nene, because it's a 3D live this time!
はい、というわけで、今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
Anyway, here's the hashtag for today!
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 です！
It's #MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026!
今ね、エゴサの機能がちょっとバグっちゃってるんで、
Right now, the ego-search function is bugging out a bit,
こっちでツイートしてくれたらめっちゃ嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
so I'd be really happy if you tweet with this! Thanks in advance!
今日はね、超重大告知があるので、最後まで楽しんでいってください！
Today, there's a super major announcement, so please enjoy until the very end!
さあ、今3曲お聞きいただいたんですけど、
Now, you've just heard three songs,
ねねの好きな曲、銀魂、バカテス、っていう感じで、
Nene's favorite songs, like Gintama and BakaTest,
もうねねの好きな曲しかない3曲をやりましたけど、
I've performed three songs that are nothing but my favorites,
3曲目に一番、歌が、歌がきついの持ってきちゃって、
but I brought the most vocally demanding one as the third song,
ゼーハーゼーハーでございます。
so I'm completely out of breath.
というわけで、ここからはゲストパート入っていきます！
So, from here on, we're moving into the guest part!
それでは、VTR、レッツゴー！
Now then, VTR, let's go!
抱きしめたいんだ (PAN-PAN-PAN)
I want to hug you! (PAN-PAN-PAN)
噛みしめたいんだ (MON-MON)
I want to chew through this! (MON-MON)
驚かしたいんだ 今は我慢しよ
I want to shock you! But I'll hold it back for now
COOLISH WALK
with a COOLISH WALK
[Song: COOLISH WALK]
平常心が大事です (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
Having a peaceful heart is important. (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
ハやるココロを抑えて (MON-MON-MON-MON)
Hold back your speeding-up heart. (MON-MON-MON-MON)
正直者になりましょう (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
Let's be straightforward! (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
ヤバイ人ならすぐなれる
You can always become dangerous.
青い 二人の天国
A blue heaven for the two of us.
子犬になる夢は レア
A dream in which I become a puppy is rare.
憂鬱ダブル盛りの脳
I have a brain of double-scoops of melancholy
トレースして
As I trace,
(空を駆け回りたい)
(I want to go around the sky).
揺れる思いの下の果肉には
The flesh of the fruit that's underneath my swaying feelings
恋の美味しさだけ 膨らんでる
Swells out only with the beauty of falling in love.
すごいメニューを作る 野望なら
If you feel ambition when you make a great menu,
まともなフルーツ 育みましょう
Let's bring up some decent fruits.
高まりたいんだ (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
I want to be loud! (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
味わいたいんだ (MON-MON)
I want to take a taste! (MON-MON)
おたけびたいんだ そんな夢をみて
I want to give a war cry! I have that kind of dream
COOLISH WALK
when I'm on a COOLISH WALK...
対抗心は危険です (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
An antagonistic heart is dangerous. (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
イラつく午後は深呼吸 (MON-MON-MON-MON)
On afternoons that get you irritated, take a deep breath. (MON-MON-MON-MON)
優雅な大人気取りましょう (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
Let's have some affection for those elegant adults. (PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN)
キレる人は余ってる
These days, people who lose it are increasing.
甘い 温度のソファで
In a sofa with a sweet temperature,
甘い温度のソファー
ミルクなささやきは (コア)
a milky whisper is (the core).
無限 ループする愛イメージして
Let's imagine love in an eternal loop
(街を 飛び跳ねよう)
(and hop around the town).
すまし顔で無視の ほっぺたに
I turn my cheek and ignore him with a composed face.
意外なお願いが 詰まってる
There's an unsuspected request waiting.
誰も知らないストーリー 恐れないで
In a story nobody knows, don't fear it.
まっすぐ ゴールを つきつめましょう
Let's think through the goal straight-forwardly.
パンパンパン パン・パンパンパンパン パンパン…
PAN-PAN-PAN PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN...
遠いあこがれヘヴン
I sometimes lose sight of
時々見うしなう (ティアー)
The heaven I admire, so far away. (Tear)
無念・涙のかけらイレースしよう
Let's erase shards of regret and teardrops.
(ユーウツ 片付けよう)
(Let's clean away the melancholy.)
揺れる想いの下の 果肉には
The flesh of the fruit that's underneath my swaying feelings
恋の美味しさだけ ふくらんでる
Swells out only with the beauty of falling in love.
凄いメニューを作ると 野望なら
If you feel ambition when you make a great menu,
まっとうに フルーツ はぐくみましょう
Let's bring up some decent fruits.
抱きしめたいんだ!(パンパンパン)
I want to hug you! (PAN-PAN-PAN)
かみしめたいんだ!(モンモン)
I want to chew through this! (MON-MON)
おどかしたいんだ!
I want to shock you!
今は我慢しよう (パンパンパン)
But I'll hold it back for now (PAN-PAN-PAN)
修行しよう (パンパンパン)
I'll train myself (PAN-PAN-PAN)
気合いしよう COOLISH WALK…
And get fired up with a COOLISH WALK...
パンパンパン パン・パンパンパンパン パンパン…
PAN-PAN-PAN PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN-PAN...
フレンズ
作詞：NOKKO 作曲：土橋安騎夫
[Friends]
Lyrics: NOKKO / Composition: Akio Dobashi
口づけを かわした日は
The day we kissed,
ママの顔さえも見れなかった
I couldn't even look at my mom's face.
ポケットのコイン あつめて
I gathered up my pocket coins
ひとつずつ 夢をかぞえたね
one by one, counting our dreams.
ほら あれは二人の
Look, that was our
かくれがひみつのメモリー
two-person hideout, a secret memory.
oh どこで こわれたの oh フレンズ
Oh, where did it break? Oh Friends.
うつむく日は みつめあって指をつないだら
On days when we looked down, we stared at each other and held hands,
oh フレンズ 時がとまる 気がした
oh Friends, I felt like time stopped.
ねぇ 君は 覚えている
Hey, do you remember?
夕映えによくにあうあの曲
That song that goes well with the sunset.
だまりこむ 君がいつも悲しくて
You were always sad and silent,
口ずさんだのに
even though you were humming it.
今 時は流れて
But now time flows,
セピアに染まるメロディー
a melody dyed in sepia.
oh 二度と もどれない oh フレンズ
Oh, we can never go back, oh Friends.
他人よりも 遠く見えていつも走ってた
Looking further away than others, we were always running.
oh フレンズ あの瞳が いとしい
Oh Friends, those eyes are dear.
chu chu yeah!
please me!
without you!
青空のラプソディ / 作詞：林英樹 作曲：佐藤純一
[Title: Aozora no Rhapsody / Lyrics: Hideki Hayashi, Music: Junichi Sato]
あー！なんてことだ 些細な過ちだ
Ah! What's this, a trivial mistake?
自分のことにタララッタラッタ手焼く
I'm fiddling with things of my own
どうして突然？逃げ切ったっていいでしょ？
Why so sudden? It's fine to just run away, right?
だけどなんだか気まぐれモードになり
But somehow, I'm in a whim mode
そんな気分になっちゃって
And I ended up in that mood
始まりはそんな風で
It started like that
つまりはらしくないようで
In short, it doesn't seem like me
でも今じゃ扉開けてほら 声が聴こえるよ
But now I open the door and look, I can hear your voice
さあ！行こう！ どこへでも
Come on! Let's go! Anywhere!
僕は君の翼に なれる勇気があるよ！
I have the courage to become your wings!
(please stay with me)
どんな試練も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any trials
その魔法があるから
Because I have that magic
(なんてったってコングラッチュレーション！)
(Congratulations, no matter what!)
初めて出会う世界に 花束を贈ろう
Let's give a bouquet to the world we meet for the first time
(made in society)
ただこの瞬間結ばれるよ
Just in this moment, we are connected
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション？
Incoherent communication?
でも別に構わない 明日から平和なら！
But I don't care, as long as it's peaceful from tomorrow!
chu chu yeah! without you!
あー！どうしてまた素直になれなくて
Ah! Why can't I be honest again?
自分のことでチュルルッチュルッチュ火吹く
I'm blowing fire with my own things
ギアはそのまま スピード上げていこう
Gear is as is, let's turn up the speed
だけどなんだか黄昏モードになり
But somehow, I'm in a twilight mode
いつかを思い出しちゃって
And I ended up remembering someday
一人でいても嫌じゃない
Even if I'm alone, it's not bad
誰にも頼らなくてもいい
I don't have to rely on anyone
でも扉の向こう騒がしい 声が聞きたいよ
But I want to hear the noisy voice beyond the door
今！行こう！ どこへでも
Now! Let's go! Anywhere!
僕は君を背中に 乗せて空を舞うよ！
I will carry you on my back and fly in the sky!
(please fly with me)
いつか心が離れても
Even if our hearts drift apart someday
その時は笑ってて
At that time, keep smiling
(なんてったってコングラッチュレーション)
(Congratulations, no matter what)
守りたいこの世界に 青空のラプソディ
In this world I want to protect, an Aozora no Rhapsody
(make me rhapsodic!)
ただいつまでも奏でていてよ
Just keep playing it forever
凸凹なコンビネーション？
Uneven combination?
でも別に大丈夫さ 明日はまた平和だ！
But it's fine, tomorrow will be peaceful again!
ほんの小さな傷を 太陽にさらして
Expose a tiny wound to the sun
分け合ったよ君と 痛みは熱さの中に溶けてく！
I shared it with you, the pain dissolves into the heat!
chu chu yeah! 粋なビート弾く僕ら！
chu chu yeah! We play a chic beat!
please me! 手を叩いて
please me! Clap your hands
chu chu yeah! ブギーなリズムではしゃぐ二人！
chu chu yeah! Two people frolicking in a boogie rhythm!
without you! 飛び跳ねてさ
without you! Jump around
chu chu yeah! 粋なビート弾く僕ら！
chu chu yeah! We play a chic beat!
please me! 手を叩いて
please me! Clap your hands
chu chu yeah! ブギーなリズムではしゃぐアリーナ！
chu chu yeah! The arena frolicking in a boogie rhythm!
どこまでも！
Anywhere!
僕は君の翼に なれる勇気があるよ！
I have the courage to become your wings!
(please stay with me)
どんな試練も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any trials
その魔法があるから
Because I have that magic
(なんてったってコングラッチュレーション)
(Congratulations, no matter what)
君と出会い世界は 花束に溢れた
Meeting you, the world overflowed with bouquets
(made in society)
ただその瞬間結ばれたよ
Just in that moment, we were connected
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション？
Incoherent communication?
進別に構わない 明日が平和なら
But I don't care, as long as tomorrow is peaceful
chu chu yeah! please me! 息を切らしwithout you！
chu chu yeah! please me! Out of breath, without you!
青春のラプソディ
[Title: Seishun no Rhapsody]
逃げない 負けない
Don't run away, don't give up
止めない 辞めない
Don't stop, don't quit
足りない 消せない
Not enough, can't erase
拙い 言葉は いらない
Immature words, not needed
覚めない しょげない
Don't wake up, don't get depressed
折れない
Don't break
もう一回
One more time
逃げない 負けない 止めない 辞めない
Don't run away, don't give up, don't stop, don't quit
足りない 消せない
Not enough, can't erase
感情ぐるぐる ないないの歌
Emotions swirling, a song of not-at-all
青春Ready Go! Wow oh oh oh...
Youth, Ready Go! Wow oh oh oh...
どこまでも
Anywhere
僕は君の翼に
I will be your wings
なれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to become them
どんな試練も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any trial
その魔法があるから
Because of that magic
君と出会い世界は
Meeting you, the world
花束にあふれた
Overflowed with bouquets
ただその瞬間を待っていたよ
I was just waiting for that moment
ちぐはぐコミュニケーション
Awkward communication
でも別に構わない
But I don't really mind
明日が平和なら
If tomorrow is peaceful
はい！やりきったー！
Yes! We did it!
やりきりました！
We did it!
ねね間違えたけど、
Nene made a mistake,
多分気づかれてないから大丈夫。
but it's probably fine because no one noticed.
私も間違えました。
I also made a mistake.
あ、間違えた？
Oh, you did?
大丈夫、みんな大丈夫。
It's okay, everyone's okay.
バレてない。
It wasn't noticed.
というわけで今日はねねのお誕生日の記念ライブに、
So, today for Nene's birthday memorial live,
可愛い後輩二人に来てもらいました！
we have two cute juniors here!
ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとう！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
デビューしてからの目標が、先輩と一緒にステージで歌って踊ることやったから、
Since my debut, my goal was to sing and dance on stage with my seniors,
それが今日叶ったのが、本当に良かったです！
so I'm really glad that came true today!
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
えー、じゃあちょっと最後に可愛くポーズ決めて、
Well then, let's strike a cute pose at the end,
写真撮って、終わりにしようかなと思います。
take a photo, and then finish up.
全力でみんなそれぞれ可愛いポーズ！
Everyone, do your best cute pose!
せーの！
Ready, set...
イエーイ！
Yay!
あれ？二人とも可愛くないじゃないの！
Wait? You two aren't being cute!
裏切ったわ！
You betrayed me!
Realize!
[Title: Realize!]
無口な ハート開いたら
When you open your silent heart
進もう
Let's move forward
声合わせて キラキラ
Combine our voices and sparkle
している自分を 掴もう
Let's grab our sparkling selves
大好きな事しよう
Let's do what we love
勝ちか負けだなんて 関係ないじゃないっ！
Winning or losing doesn't matter, right!
さあ手と手つないで Hey Jump!
Come on, hold hands, Hey Jump!
パーティは始まる Let's Dance 1,2,3!
The party is starting, Let's Dance 1, 2, 3!
未来へ そうずっと みんなで
To the future, always, with everyone
絶対あきらめたくないから
Because I absolutely don't want to give up
Let's sing Do my best!
明日はきっと輝いてる
Tomorrow will surely shine
力合わせて トキメキ探してく
Combine our strength and search for excitement
つかみ取ろうプリパラ
Let's grab it, PriPara!
どんな壁だって 問題ないじゃないっ！
It doesn't matter what kind of wall is in the way, right!
さぁ勇気を出して
Come, show your courage
Hey Clap 夢が始まる
Hey Clap! The dream begins
Let's Dance Run with me 未来へそうずっと
Let's Dance Run with me! To the future, always
みんなで
everyone together
絶対手放したくないから
Because I absolutely don't want to let go
Let's Sing Believe my way 明日はもっと輝いてる
Let's Sing Believe my way! Tomorrow will shine even more
希望かかげてドキドキ探してく
Let's hold up our hope and search for thrills
誰のものプリパラ
Who does it belong to, PriPara
うまくいかないとか すれ違いばかりで
Things don't go well, it's just passing each other by
ダメになりそうな時は一緒に
When it feels like we'll be useless, let's be together
ふたつ折りの夢を叶えよう
Let's fulfill our two-folded dreams
(ずっとね)
(Always)
笑顔受け取ろう
Let's receive the smiles
そう一緒に歌いたい
Yes, I want to sing together
ねぇ一緒に踊りたい
hey, I want to dance together
絶対あきらめないよ
I absolutely won't give up
Let's Go
Let's Dance 1,2,3！ 未来へ そうずっと
Let's Dance 1, 2, 3! To the future, always
みんなで
everyone together
絶対あきらめたくないから
Because I absolutely don't want to give up
Let's sing Do my best！ 明日はきっと輝いてる
Let's sing Do my best! Tomorrow will surely shine
力合わせて トキメキ探してく
Let's combine our strength and search for excitement
つかみ取ろうプリパラ
Let's grab it, PriPara
はーい！ありがとうございます！
Hi! Thank you very much!
Let's dance! Let's dance! Let's dance!
みんなでー！
Everyone together!
いえーい！
Yay!
いったん！ねねお誕生日おめでとう！
First of all! Nene, happy birthday!
おめでとうー！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ちょっとね、コメントと30秒くらい差があるんだって。
Apparently, there's about a 30-second delay with the comments.
あ、そうなの？
Oh, really?
そう、だからまた後で！
Yeah, so we'll see them later!
一方的に話しかけることも...
We might just keep talking at you...
お邪魔してまーす！
Thanks for having us!
はい！っていうか、おまる！
Yes! Anyway, Omaru!
いや、マジでさ、Realize!
Seriously, Realize!
本当にこの4人なのがもうめちゃくちゃエモすぎて！
Having these four together is just so emotional!
エモかったね！
It was emotional!
メンゲン！メンゲンにしよう！
Members-only! Let's do a members-only stream!
おまるんさ、後であるから！
Omaru-n, we'll do that later!
おまるん、ちょっと飛べるようになった。
Omaru-n can fly a little now.
メンゲンでお教えします！
I'll teach you in members-only!
メンゲン？
Members-only?
見てねー！
Watch it!
みんな見てねー！
Everyone, watch it!
メンゲン！後でまた会いましょう！
Members-only! Let's meet again later!
メンゲン暴れ！
Members-only rampage!
時間ない時間ない！
No time, no time!
あ、ポーズ撮らないと！
Oh, we have to take a pose!
ポーズ撮って、いくよ！
Take a pose, here we go!
もちろん！面白いポーズで！
Of course! With a funny pose!
面白いポーズまで、3、2、1...
A funny pose in 3, 2, 1...
うわぁぁぁ！
Uwaaa!
君セン！
[Title: Kimi Sen!]
Ready... あたし始めない...
Ready... Don't start without me...
なんてね！
Just kidding!
トーストかじって
Biting into toast
交差点でぶつかる
Colliding at the intersection
そういうのじゃないけど
It's not like that, but
予感はしてたよ
I had a feeling
必然？ 運命？
Inevitability? Fate?
会えるって信じてた
I believed we'd meet
君専用の笑顔 100点満点 OK!
A smile just for you, 100 points OK!
口が滑ったり ため息ついたり
Slipping up with words, sighing
あるよね わかるよ
It happens, I understand
君が寂しくて泣いてるなら
If you're lonely and crying
イライラしてたまらないなら
If you're so frustrated you can't stand it
あたしの出番だ！とその手を取って連れてくよ
It's my turn! I'll take your hand and lead you away
ようこそ無敵なテーマパーク
Welcome to the invincible theme park
嫌な事全部忘れちゃえ
Forget all the bad things
とりあえずは あたしだけ見て
For now, just look at me
底なしの沼だぞ ちょっと考えられないくらい
It's a bottomless pit, almost unthinkable
愛をあげる
I'll give you love
君が好きだ
I love you
Ready... あたし始めない...
Ready... Don't start without me...
どうやらフラグはまだ 立っていないみたいだ
Looks like the flag hasn't been set yet.
そんなの気にしない 一直線にTrue end
I don't care about that. Straight to the True end.
きっとね (やっぱね!)
It's sure (As I thought!)
安定だね (そうだね!)
Stable (That's right!)
お決まりのツーショット
A classic two-shot,
2人っきりの空間
a space just for the two of us.
スタンバイオッケー!
Standby OK!
舞いあがっちゃって あとで反省会
Soaring high, reflecting on it later,
あるよねわかるよ
it happens, I understand.
脳内占拠して 眠れないなら
If I take over your brain and you can't sleep,
ソワソワして たまらないなら
if you're so restless you can't stand it,
いつだっておいでよ
always come to me.
少しずつ 積み上げていこう
Let's build it up little by little.
ようこそ! 無限のパーリータイム
Welcome! To the infinite party time.
もういっそ ずっと一緒にいよう
Better just be together forever.
とことんまで 笑っていてね
Keep laughing until the end.
もっと知って欲しいんだぞ
I want you to know more.
そっと掴んだシャツの裾
Holding the hem of the shirt I grabbed softly.
最上級を プレゼントしよう
I'll present you with the highest class.
深く考えなくてもいいよ
You don't have to think deeply,
ただ『楽しい』を 続けよう!
just keep having 'fun'!
繋いだ今日が 明日になってくんだ
The day we joined is becoming tomorrow.
ヨーソロー! 全速前進で
Yo-Ho-Ro! Full speed ahead,
とんでもない景色 見に行こう
Let's go see a scene you wouldn't believe.
乗りかかってる 自覚あるでしょ?
You're aware you're getting into it, right?
そんじゃそこらの 遊びじゃ もう満足できないくらい
With play like that, I can't be satisfied anymore.
夢中になれる
I can get obsessed,
夢中にさせる
I can make you obsessed.
ようこそ! 無敵のテーマパーク
Welcome! To the invincible theme park.
もういっそ 全部忘れちゃえ!
Better just forget everything!
とりあえずは あたしだけ見て
For now, just look at me.
底なしの沼だぞ
It's a bottomless swamp.
ちょっと 考えられないくらい 愛をあげる
I can't even think about it, I'll give you love.
君が好きだ
I like you.
時間なんて 関係ないさ
Time doesn't matter.
今だってほら 笑ってんじゃん
Look, you're laughing even now.
提案です! あたし始めない?
Proposal! Shall I start?
なんてね
Just kidding.
ギターと孤独と蒼い惑星
[Title: Guitar, Loneliness and Blue Planet]
突然降る夕立 あぁ傘もないや嫌
Sudden evening shower, ah, I don't even have an umbrella.
空のご機嫌なんか知らない
I don't know the sky's mood.
季節の変わり目の服は 何着りゃいいんだろ
Clothes for the change of seasons, what should I wear?
春と秋 どこいっちゃったんだよ
Spring and autumn, where did they go?
息も出来ない
Can't even breathe,
情報の圧力
information pressure,
めまいの螺旋だ
a spiral of dizziness.
わたしはどこにいる
Where am I?
こんなに こんなに
Even though I can hear
息の音がするのに
my breathing so clearly, so clearly.
変だね
Strange,
世界の音がしない
I don't hear the sounds of the world.
足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough,
誰にも気づかれない
no one notices me.
殴り書きみたいな音
Scribbled sounds,
出せない状態で叫んだよ
couldn't put them out, I screamed in that state,
「ありのまま」なんて
"as I am",
誰に見せるんだ
who am I showing that to?
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
I, a stupid person, just sing.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Should I spill it all out? To the stars.
エリクサーに張り替える作業もなんとなくなんだ
Changing to elixir strings is just something I do.
欠けた爪を少し触る
Touching the chipped nails a little
半径300mmの体で 必死に鳴いてる
with a body of 300mm radius, frantically singing.
音楽にとっちゃ ココが地球だな
To music, this place is Earth.
空気を握って
Grasping the air,
空を殴るよ
punching the sky,
なんにも起きない
nothing happens.
わたしは無力さ
I am helpless.
だけどさ その手で
But, if I strike
この鉄を弾いたら
this iron with that hand,
何かが変わって見えた…ような。
something changed... it seemed like.
眩しい 眩しい
Dazzling, dazzling,
そんなに光るなよ
don't shine so brightly.
わたしのダサい影が
My uncool shadow
より色濃くなってしまうだろ
will become even darker, won't it?
なんでこんな熱くなっちゃってんだ
Why have I become so hot?
止まんない
It won't stop.
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
Foolish me, I just sing.
うるさいんだって
"It's noisy,"
心臓
says my heart.
はい！
Yes!
ねね先輩お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you!
イェーイ！
Yay!
というわけで、ReGLOSSから奏ちゃんに
And so, we have Kanade-chan from ReGLOSS
来てもらいました！
here to join us!
ヤッホー！轟奏です！
Yahoo! I'm Kanade Todoroki!
来ちゃいましたよー！
I'm here!
今回はね、ねね、普段の奏ちゃんとの
This time, Nene really loves
喋りと歌のギャップが大好きで...
the gap between Kanade's talk and her singing...
はあ！
Haa!
普段これじゃんｗ
Usually she's like this lol
普段これだけど歌うと急に、ね、
Usually like this, but when she sings, suddenly
なんか、切ないエモいみたいな...
it's like, painful and emotional...
え、嬉しい！ねね先輩にそう言って
Eh, I'm so happy! To hear that
もらえるととっても嬉しいです！
from you, Nene-senpai, I'm very happy!
本当！そのイメージがめっちゃ好きで、
Really! I like that image so much,
一緒に何かそういうちょっとギャップが
and I wanted to sing a song together
出る曲歌いたいなと思って...
that shows that gap...
ねね先輩もめっちゃかっこよかったです！
Nene-senpai was also very cool!
ありがとう！最高ー！
Thank you! The best!
あと何か髪の毛の色もさ...
And also the hair color...
確かに！
True!
同じ金髪...
The same blonde...
イエローからピンクのグラデーション...
Yellow to pink gradation...
そんな感じのナチュラルかなと思って、
I thought it was natural like that,
お誘いしてみました。
so I invited you.
受けてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for accepting!
こちらこそ！ありがとうございます！
Likewise! Thank you very much!
一緒に歌えてとっても嬉しかったです！
I was very happy to sing with you!
奏ちゃんのね、ダンスの覚え方が可愛いんだよ。
Kanade's way of remembering the dance is cute.
え、そうですか？
Eh, really?
なんか、ニンジャ、ニンジャ、ニンジャ...
Like, ninja, ninja, ninja...
覚え方がこう、こうなってて、
The way of remembering was like this,
ニンジャニンジャｗ
ninja ninja lol
ニンジャちゃんもめっちゃ笑顔だったよ。
Ninja-chan was also smiling a lot.
えっと、じゃあ、最後にちょっと
Um, well, finally,
どうしようかな...
what should we do...
ギャップのある感じで、
With a gap-filled feel,
スクショタイムさせてください。
please let us do a screenshot time.
任せてください。
Leave it to me.
任せてくださいなの？ｗ
"Leave it to me"? lol
ちょっといけるかな、ねねも。ちょっとかっこいい
I wonder if I can do it too, Nene. In a cool,
エモい感じで。孤独な感じで。
emotional way. With a lonely feel.
任せてください。いきますよ。
Leave it to me. Here we go.
いっせーのーで。
One, two...
オホッｗ
Oho lol
今なんて？何やった今？ｗ
What was that? What did you do just now? lol
ちょっとかっこいいエモい感じで。
In a cool emotional way.
オホ、オホｗ
Oho, oho lol
オホｗ
Oho lol
サクラが咲くよ
Sakura blossoms fall,
見慣れたいつもの坂道に
on the usual slope I'm so familiar with.
ああ　別れを
Ah, a parting...
さよならメモリーズ
作詞・作曲：ryo (supercell)
[Title: Sayonara Memories]
[Lyrics & Music: ryo (supercell)]
泣いて笑ったあの日々
Those days of crying and laughing,
なんだか昨日のことのよう
they feel like they were only yesterday.
さよならメモリーズ
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026
[Sayonara Memories]
[#MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026]
この道はそう
This road, you see,
未来へ
towards the future,
続く道
is the road that continues on.
そんな気がしたの
That's how it felt to me.
例年より早い
Earlier than most years,
開花予想を
the cherry blossom forecast...
君は嬉しがってた
you were so happy about it.
私は笑って
I smiled and said,
「そうだね」って言った
"I guess so."
あと少ししたらもう
In just a little while longer,
ここには戻れないのに
we won't be able to come back here anymore.
言葉じゃうまく言えない思いを
These feelings I can't put into words...
君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて
if I were to open my heart to you...
伝えよう
How should I say it?
最初で最後
The first and the last.
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The road we once walked home together on
私にとって特別な思い出
is a special memory for me.
忘れないよ
I won't forget,
さよならメモリーズ
those goodbye memories.
春が来たら
When spring comes,
それぞれの道を
we'll go our separate ways.
また会える日を願って
Praying for the day we can meet again,
さよなら
"Goodbye,"
小さくつぶやいた
I softly whispered.
空はあの日と変わらず
The sky was just like that day,
青くて
so blue,
だからちょっと泣けた
that it made me cry a little.
わざと遠回りしたの
I purposely took the long way around,
少しでも長く
just to stay a little bit longer
君の隣にいたくて
by your side.
私はおどけて
I jokingly said,
「間違えた」って言った
"I took the wrong turn."
君が笑うその顔が
The way you smiled was so radiant
まぶしくて目をそらした
that I looked away.
言葉じゃうまく言えない思いを
These feelings I can't put into words...
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
I held them in my heart as we walked this road.
覚えてる?
Do you remember?
あの時君は
Back then, you...
私の名前を呼んでくれた
you called my name.
二人夕暮れの帰り道で
On our way home together at dusk.
忘れないよ
I won't forget,
さよならメモリーズ
those goodbye memories.
出会えたこと
I'm grateful
感謝してる
that we met.
初めて見た
For the first time, we saw
満開の桜
the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
あれからどれくらい
How much have I...
変われたんだろう
managed to change since then?
一目見た時に思ったんだ
The first time I saw you, I thought,
この人のこと好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall for this person."
なんでかな
I wonder why?
わかんないよ
I don't even know.
それからの毎日とても
Every day since then has been so fun,
楽しくてだけど同じくらいに
but at the same time,
辛かったんだ
it's been just as painful.
ごめんねなんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't express it very well.
だから私君となんていうか
So, I... with you... how should I say it?
今のまま
As things are now...
さよならしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye.
友達のままじゃ
Remaining just friends...
もう嫌なの
I don't want that anymore!
言おうと思ってた
I've been planning to tell you.
私君の
I... you...
君のことずっと
about you, I've always...
ずっと
always...
前から
for a long time...
好きでした
been in love with you.
やっと言えた
I finally said it.
[曲：さよならメモリーズ]
[Song: Sayonara Memories]
[曲：ODDS&ENDS]
[Song: ODDS&ENDS]
いつだって君は嗤われ者だ
You are always someone who is laughed at
やることなすことツイてなくて
Having rotten luck in all that you do,
挙句に雨に降られ
Being rained on in the end
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella has been blown away by the wind,
そこのノラはご苦労様と
The stray cat there says "thanks for your hard work"
足を踏んづけてった
and steps on your foot
いつもどおり君は嫌われものだ
Just like always you are a hated person
何にもせずとも遠ざけられて
Kept at a distance without a reason
努力をしてみるけど
Though you always try and make your best effort
その理由なんて「なんとなく？」で
With the reason being something like “Well, I’m not really sure…”
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
You were at a loss and feeling sad
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
If that’s the case, you should use my voice!
人によっては理解不能で
Though it’s not understood by some,
なんて耳障り、ひどい声だって言われるけど
Even though it’s called “ear-grating”,
“an awful voice”
きっと君の力になれる
It will surely become your strength
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So try and let me sing,
そう君の、君だけの言葉でさ
Yes, let me sing your very own words
綴って 連ねて
Compose them and join them together
あたしがその思想(コトバ)を叫ぶから
Since I’ll cry out those words
描いて 理想を
Describe your ideals,
その思いは誰にも 触れさせない
No one will be allowed to touch those feelings of yours
ガラクタの声はそして響く
And then the voice of rubbish (Odds & Ends) will ring out
ありのままを不器用につないで
Clumsily tying together things as they are
目一杯に 大声を上げる
Raising a big voice with all one’s might
いつからか君は人気者だ
One day you became a famous person
沢山の人にもてはやされ あたしも鼻が高い
Praised by so many, I was proud as well
でもいつからか君は変わった
Eventually something about you changed
冷たくなって だけど寂しそうだった
You become cold, and yet seemingly lonely all the same
「もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
“Enough with this mechanical voice already,
僕は僕自身なんだよ」って
I’ll be my own person!”
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
In the end you were unable to keep yourself from
あたしを嫌った
hating me
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Behind your back, someone said,
「虎の威を借る狐のくせに」って
“Even though all this fame is not his own doing…”
君は ひとりで泣いてたんだね
Hey, you were crying all alone weren’t you?
聴こえる？この声
Can you hear it? This voice of mine.
あたしがその言葉を掻き消すから
Since I’ll drown out those hurtful words
解ってる本当は 君が誰より優しいってことを
I know the truth, that you really are kinder than anyone else
ガラクタの声はそして歌った 他の誰でもない君のために
And then the voice of rubbish sang for no one but you alone,
軋んでく 限界を超えて
Squeaking alone, crossing over boundaries
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を
The two of us came up with lots of words
思いついたことだろう
together didn’t we?
だけど今は何ひとつ思いつかなくて
Though we’re not able to come up with a single one right now
だけどなにもかもわかった
And yet everything is understood
「そうか、きっとこれは夢だ。
“I see, surely this is a dream.
永遠に覚めない、君と会えた、そんな夢」
That dream where I met you,
one that I'll never wake up from."
ガラクタは幸せそうな表情をしたまま
With a happy expression on its face, the rubbish
どれだけ呼んでももう動かない
no longer moves, no matter how much you call out to it
望んだはずの結末に君は泣き叫ぶ
At the conclusion you should have wanted, you cry out
嘘だろ 嘘だろって そう泣き叫ぶ
“It's a lie, it's a lie,” so you cry out
「僕は無力だ。ガラクタ一つだって救えやしない」
“I'm powerless.
I can't even save a single piece of rubbish.”
想いは涙に ぽつりぽつりとその頬を濡らす
Emotions turn to tears,
wetting those cheeks drop by drop
想いは涙に
Feelings become tears...
ぽつりぽつりとその頬を濡らす
...wetting those cheeks drop by drop.
その時 世界は
At that moment, the world...
途端にその色を
...suddenly changes its colors...
大きく変える
...in a major way.
悲しみ 喜び
Sadness and joy...
全てを一人とひとつは知った
...one person and one machine learned it all.
言葉は歌になりこの世界を
Words become a song and travel this world...
再び駆け巡る 君のために
...once again, all for you.
その声に意思を宿して
Infusing that voice with a will...
今 思いが響く
...now, these feelings resonate.
はーい、ポルカがハモリじゃないよみんな
Hey! It wasn't Polka doing the harmonies, everyone!
ねねの声だよ
It's Nene's voice!
というわけで、えっと、ゲストにいっぱいに来ていただきまして
So, um, we had so many guests come today,
いっぱい色んな歌歌えて楽しかったです
and it was so much fun getting to sing so many songs.
ちなみにFriendsは、ママのチョイスです
By the way, "Friends" was Mama's choice.
みんなママのチョイスかなーって言ってたから大正解です
Everyone was guessing it was her choice, so you were spot on!
じゃあ、告知いきたいと思います
Now, I'd like to move on to some announcements.
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
桃鈴ねね 誕生記念2026 グッズ発売
[Title: Momosuzu Nene Birthday Anniversary 2026] Merch Release!
まずはこちら、ワイドラバーマット！
First, this: the Wide Rubber Mat!
上目遣いでねねが、上を見ながら、みんなにお願いってしてるイラストで
It features an illustration of Nene looking up at everyone with pleading eyes.
イラストは、まろの先生書き下ろしで
The illustration was specially drawn by Marono-sensei.
横幅がめっちゃ広いので
It's really wide, so...
キーボードとかマウス置いてデスクで使ってください
...please use it on your desk for your keyboard and mouse!
そして次はこちら！
And next is this!
さっきと同じキービジュアルを使った、前面はTシャツ
A T-shirt using the same key visual on the front.
後面は「尊き桃鈴」って書いてあるTシャツです
On the back, it says "Precious Momosuzu."
前出した「やっぱり桃鈴」に続く「尊き桃鈴」のTシャツが出来上がりました
This "Precious Momosuzu" T-shirt follows the "After All, Momosuzu" one I released before.
これもぜひ着てください
Please be sure to wear this one too!
「尊い」か「やっぱり」か選んでください。そして次は、こちら！
Choose between "Precious" or "After All." And next up...
ランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！
...Random Mini Acrylic Stand Key Holders!
いろんな衣装のねねが、可愛いポーズをしています
It features Nene in various outfits doing cute poses.
イラストは花森ゆのき先生に書いてもらいました
The illustrations were drawn by Hanamori Yunoki-sensei.
台座とね、ボールチェーンがついてるので
They come with a base and a ball chain...
ミニアクスタとしても使えるし、キーホルダーとしても使えます
...so they can be used as mini acrylic stands or key holders!
そして次、こちら！
And next, this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー、私服衣装バージョン！
Plushie Key Holder, Private Outfit version!
これめっちゃこだわって作ってて、もう可愛さ全振りの
I put a lot of thought into this; it's 100% pure cuteness!
ねね、私服衣装のぬいぐるみのキーホルダーになります
It's a plushie key holder of Nene in her private outfit.
ボールチェーン付きなので、カバンとかにつけて一緒にお出かけしてほしいな
It has a ball chain, so I hope you'll attach it to your bag and go out together.
前の、前髪とか、顔とか、すごいこだわって作ったので
I was really particular about the bangs and the face...
絶対可愛い自信あるので、実物今度見せたいと思います
...so I'm confident it's adorable! I'll show you the real thing soon.
そしてラスト、ボイスです！
And finally, the voices!
「きみとねねのお誕生日」
Situation Voice: "Birthday for You and Nene."
ねねがね、みんなのお誕生日も祝ってあげたいと思います、しょうがないので
I want to celebrate everyone's birthdays too... since I have no choice!
今すぐ聴いてもいいし、自分の誕生日に聴いてもよし！
You can listen to it right away, or wait until your actual birthday!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here is the Full Set Purchase Bonus!
数量限定は、直筆サインと複製の、箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード
The limited quantity set includes a hand-signed postcard with a foil-stamped message.
そして通常版は、箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入っています
And the regular version has a foil-stamped printed signature and message.
数量限定版今回ありますので、みなさんよろしくお願いします
We have the limited edition this time, so please check it out!
さらにボイスもついてきます！タイトル...
It also comes with a voice track! The title is...
「毎日一番に見てほしいの」ということで
..."I Want You to Look at Me First Every Day."
ねねが幼馴染のねねがね、みんなに行こうぜ行こうぜって
It's a situation voice where Nene, as your childhood friend...
朝から乗っかかってくるシチュエーションボイスあります
...comes to pester you from the morning to "Let's go, let's go!"
特典もたくさんあるので、ぜひフルセットで買ってください
There are lots of bonuses, so please consider the full set!
この後21時30分から販売開始です。よろしくお願いします！
Sales start today at 21:30. Thank you!
そして、オリ曲のMVが出ます！
Also, an MV for an original song is coming out!
「Liminal」。本日MVは21時15分からを予定しています
[Title: Liminal] The MV is scheduled for 21:15 today.
リリースは3月3日の0時から。よろしくお願いします！
The digital release is at midnight on March 3rd. Please check it out!
どんな曲だろうね。今回のライブのタイトルにもなってます
I wonder what kind of song it is? It's also the title of this live show.
そして、超重大告知があります！
And, I have a super important announcement!
こちら！
This!
「Peachful Story」。桃鈴ねねのファーストアルバムが...
[Title: Peachful Story] Momosuzu Nene's first album...
この後21時...あ、今？ちょうど今？21時から始まりました！
...is starting... at 21:00... oh, right now? Just now? It's started!
イェーイ！初回版と通常版、2種類あります
Yay! There are two versions: the Limited Edition and the Regular Edition.
通常版はこちら。
Here's the Regular Edition.
りいちゅ先生が書いてくれた通常版のやつと
The Regular Edition illustrated by Riichu-sensei...
ランダムのアナザージャケットがついてきます。なんとこちら！
...comes with a random "another jacket." And look at this!
ドン！
Bam!
いなちゃんと、ラオーラちゃんに書いてもらいました！
Ina-chan and Raora-chan drew these for me!
マイク持ってるほうが、いなちゃんで、踊ってるほうがラオーラちゃんが書いてくれました
Ina-chan drew the one with the mic, and Raora-chan drew the one where I'm dancing!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
こちらは数量限定で直筆サインが入ってるので、みなさんぜひチェックしてください
These are limited and include a hand-signed copy, so please check them out!
そして限定版は...
And the Limited Edition is...
桃鈴ねね 1st Album 『Peachful Story』 完全生産限定盤
[Nene Momosuzu 1st Album "Peachful Story" Limited First Edition]
リバーシブル仕様の直筆サイン入り アナザージャケット！
A reversible, hand-signed alternative jacket!
どっちをね、表にして主役にしていいですし、
You can make either side the front and center,
なんなら2個買っていただいて、両方とも表面にして、ねねとねねを合体させてください！
Or even buy two, make both the front, and join Nene and Nene together!
そして、こちらがついてきます！
And this also comes with it!
『Peachful Story』 レコーディングブック / PRカード
["Peachful Story" Recording Book / PR Card]
レコーディングブックと、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEのカードがついてきます！
It comes with a recording book and a hololive Official Card Game card!
ねねのね、どんな感じで歌ってたとか、ここ怒られたとか、そういうのがまとまったノートになってます！
It's a notebook that summarizes things like how I sang and where I got scolded!
そして、もうひとつあります！なんとこちら！
And there's one more thing! This!
桃鈴ねね 1st EP 『ねねねねねねねね！』
[Nene Momosuzu 1st EP "NeNeNeNeNeNeNeNe!"]
ねねねねねねねね！ねねの1st EP、グッズとして出したねねのCDが復刻になります！イエーイ！
NeNeNeNeNeNeNeNe! Nene's 1st EP, the CD I released as merch, is being reissued! Yay!
これね、意外と多分持ってる人少ないんじゃないかなと思います。
I think surprisingly few people probably have this.
今までのねねのね、有名な曲たちが入っていますので、
It contains my famous songs from up until now,
こちらの復刻版もぜひ聴いて、今回のアルバムと一緒に全曲聴いて覚えてほしいなって思います！
So please listen to this reissue too, and learn all the songs along with the new album!
さて、さっきリミナルのMVの告知をしたと思うんですけど、
Now, I think I announced the MV for 'Liminal' earlier,
どんな曲か聴きたいよね、みんな！
But you all want to hear what kind of song it is, right?!
それじゃあ、ねね今からしっとりとやっていこうかなと思います。
Then, Nene is going to perform it for you now in a soulful way.
それでは聴いてください。リミナル。
Please listen. Liminal.
見つめる
Staring...
くすんだ瞳で
...with clouded eyes
光を探して迷ってた
I was lost, searching for light
いくつもの痛みに
Bound by...
縛られたまま
...so many pains
頬を伝う
Tears stream down my cheeks
画面に映る私はどうして
Why is it that the me on the screen,
涙の跡が消されているんだろう
Has the traces of her tears erased?
罅割れた硝子の向こう
Beyond the cracked glass,
笑って繕っていた
She was smiling, putting on a front,
誰かがいた
There was someone there
「偽物みたいだ」
"It's like a fake,"
「ただの影だ」って
"It's just a shadow,"
決め付けたけど
I decided,
まやかしじゃなくて
But it's not a deception,
私が私でいる理由を
The reason why I am me...
君の笑顔に貰っていた
...I received from your smile
そうさ 画面の中
That's right, inside the screen,
隠せない
I can't hide it,
消えない
It won't disappear,
見えない
It can't be seen
それでも
Even so,
私は
I...
君の光を追って
...will follow your light,
閉じこもる暗い硝子の曇りを払って
Clearing the fog on the dark glass I was trapped behind
今 明日を見つけたんだ
Now, I've found tomorrow
忘れたくない
I don't want to forget
君がくれた この感情を
This feeling you gave me
見つめる
Staring...
姿鏡の奥の
...deep into the full-length mirror
涙の跡は見せられないけど
I can't show the traces of my tears, but...
磨かれた硝子の向こう
Beyond the polished glass,
笑って 輝いていたいだけで
I just want to be smiling and shining
「誰のためだっけ？」
"Who was it for again?"
声が
The voice...
姿が
...the figure...
誰でもない気がした
...felt like they were no one at all
「孤独だ」って
"I'm lonely,"
また迷い出す
I start to lose my way again
画面の奥の歪みを
The distortion behind the screen,
いつでも
Always,
君は
You...
映す光の中に
...within the reflected light,
名もない私の声を見つけてくれてた
Were finding my nameless voice
ずっと
All along
「この声も、姿も、紛れもない私だ」
"This voice, this form, they're unmistakably me."
「ありのままでいいんだ」
"It's all right to be just as I am."
「この気持ちは本物だ」
"This feeling is the real thing."
縛られても
Even if I'm bound,
触れられなくても
even if I can't be touched,
君が示してくれてたから
it's because you were there showing me the way.
いつか この「私」で
Someday, as this "me,"
ずっと 光を手繰って
I'll keep reaching out for the light,
きっと 見つけ出す
and I'll surely find my way,
誰でもない「君」に会えるまで
until I can meet "you," who is like no other.
境界線はすぐそこに
The boundary is right there.
そうさ 画面の向こう
That's right, beyond the screen,
繋ぎたい
I want to connect,
越えたい
I want to cross over,
触れたい
I want to touch,
それこそ それこそ 私なんだ
that is exactly, that is exactly who I am.
君と光になって
Becoming light together with you,
未だ遮る硝子の壁の先まで
to the other side of the glass wall that still blocks us,
届くように笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling so it reaches you.
迷いはない
I have no hesitations,
君がくれた この感情 と
with this feeling that you gave me...
あぁ…
Ah...